# **Agustin Mandarini**

San Carlos de Bariloche – Rio Negro, Argentina

# **Full Stack Web Developer**

agustinmandarini47@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/agustin-mandarini-8a73a4225/

GitHub: https://github.com/AgustinMandarini

Tel.: +54 9 11 39534746

My expertise is as a Full Stack Developer with a background in network systems for electronic security. I have experience in both Front End and Back End development. I enjoy working collaboratively within a team. I take pleasure in providing support and being a resource for my team, as well as requesting assistance when I deem it necessary. Throughout my experience, I have successfully completed projects that had a positive impact on the professional development of the team and on the company's value. Additionally, I have knowledge in agile methodologies, SCRUM, GIT, data structures, algorithms, Python, Django, Javascript, Node.js, Express, Sequelize, Postgres, React, Redux, HTML, and CSS frameworks. English Level: C2 Proficient.

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

## Data Logger / Report Generator App - Python | Baldor SRL

May. 2023 - Present

Developed an application for sound level measuring machines for safety and hygiene purposes. The project was entirely developed in Python, utilizing a small SQLite database, a virtual environment, and several libraries such as tkinter and matplotlib.

 ${\bf Git Hub:} \ \underline{https://github.com/AgustinMandarini/Vibrac}$ 

Baldor SRL: https://www.baldorshop.com.ar/

# Full Stack Web Developer - MSC Amobiamientos

Sep. 2023 - Nov 2023

Development of an E-Commerce platform for a furniture and furnishings startup. The application features: product rendering, product search and filtering, user registration and login system with JWT and Auth0, admin dashboard (CRUD design for users, products, sales), user domains, data persistence with local storage, shopping cart, payment system with MercadoPago, image storage with Cloudinary, responsive design, among other features.

**Front:** React, Redux, Bootstrap 4. **Back**: Node, Express y Sequelize

Base de datos: PostgreSQL y Sequelize.

Link: <a href="https://msc-amoblamientos.vercel.app/home">https://msc-amoblamientos.vercel.app/home</a>

**GitHub:** https://github.com/AgustinMandarini/MSC-Amoblamientos

## **Full Stack Teaching Assistant**

Aug. 2023 - Present

Academic experience - Henry Bootcamp

- Coordinated a group of students to facilitate their integration into the study team.
- Assisted in solving exercises and encouraged group collaboration (Pair Programming).
- Proposed ideas for improving Bootcamp processes.

Electronic Security and Telecommunications Specialist | Argentinian Army Sep 2015 - Present

- Designed electrical and telecommunications network infrastructure.
- Planned and designed electronic security systems, including the placement of devices, cameras, alarms, vibration sensors, etc.
- Coordinated installation and technical teams.
- Provided advisory and consultancy services to clients for electronic security solutions in sensitive sectors
  of the Argentinian Army.
- Configured and maintained equipment, software, and networks.

#### **PROJECTS**

## Full Stack Web Developer - Doggypedia App

Jun. 2023 - Present

Academic experience - Henry Bootcamp

Developed a Single Page Application (SPA) that consumes an API and displays information about 264 different dog breeds, allowing users to create and save new breeds in a database, search for them by name, and filter them.

Front: React

Back: Express y Sequelize

**Database:** PostgreSQL y Sequelize. **Link:** <a href="https://doggypedia-nu.vercel.app/">https://doggypedia-nu.vercel.app/</a>

**GitHub:** <a href="https://github.com/AgustinMandarini/dogsApp">https://github.com/AgustinMandarini/dogsApp</a>

## **TECHNOLOGIES:**

**Programming languages:** Javascript, Node, Python, HTML, CSS. **Frameworks:** React, Redux, Express. **Databases:** Sequelize, Postgres. **Tools:** Git, Slack. **Agile:** Scrum.

## PROFESSIONAL EDUCATION

- Completed a comprehensive Full Stack Web Developer program at Henry Bootcamp, consisting of 800 hours of theoretical and practical coursework.
- Industrial Engineering from Universidad Nacional General Sarmiento, 2011 a 2014.

#### ADDITIONAL EDUCATION

- CS50's Web Programming with Python and Javascript,
- CS50x: Introduction to Computer Science, Jul Nov 2021

# **LANGUAGES**

Spanish: Native Speaker.

English: C2 Proficient - https://www.efset.org/cert/GxHGvZ